让我们data包内创造一个天气的provider类
Let's create a weather provider class within the
我们将其作为ContentProvider的继承。
data package. We'll have it extend ContentProvider.
你可以通过使用Ctrl+I来实现需要的类函数
You can have the required method by heading
ContentProvider的功能实现是基于
Ctrl+I once more. ContentProvider implement functionality based upon
URI的。每个URI类型都被约束为一个
the URI's. Each URI type is tied to
整型常量。我们的ContentProvider将会实现五个
an integer constant. Our ContentProvider will implement five
不同类型的URI。每个
different types of URI's. Each one of these
URI会用作不同类型的需求。
URI's will be used for different types of queries.
现在，我们把这些常量加入我们的WeatherProvider类
For now, let's just add these constants into our WeatherProvider class.
Android提供一个URIMatcher类来协助
Android provides a URIMatcher class to help
URI与我们的整型常量的配对。它规定了
match URI's to our integer constants. It provides
一个表达式配对不同的URI。
for an expression syntax to match various URI's.
这里是一些例子。你将会很快把
Now these are just examples. You're going to have
他们中的一些实现。记住
to implement one of these very soon. Note,
这里有两个通配符。
that there are two wildcards.
“#”是用来通配数字的，“*”是用来通配字符串的。
The pound sign is used to match a number, while a star is used to match a string.
利用这些,你可以非常容易去匹配任何
Using this,you can very, very easily match any of the URI's
我们希望传递进入我们的ContentProvider的URI
that we would want to pass in to our ContentProvide.